amchamchina.org 2017-09-03

# Privacy Policy | AmCham Business Center

AmCham China operates at the heart of the American community in China, connecting US citizens and businesses with a vibrant, volunteer-led platform that represents American multinationals, SMEs, entrepreneurs and individuals in China.

To make this platform work effectively, our Privacy Policy helps you understand what information we are collecting and how we use it. If, after reading it, you have any questions, please contact [webmaster@amchamchina.org](mailto:webmaster@amchamchina.org). We may update this statement periodically, so please check back here for updates.

**_What We Collect and Why_**

We collect information to provide, maintain and improve our services to all of our members.

When you join AmCham China, you provide us with personal information and information about the company you work for, some of which is required by law and some of which helps the chamber provide better services to its members. 

We will also gather information about those from our member companies who use our Business Visa Service to help us process their applications.  

If you just visit our website, you may also provide us with some information when you conduct tasks such as signing up for our email newsletters or downloading various materials from the website. Coding in the website will also gather information such as where you are accessing from, what kind of systems you are using and what pages you visit that is used in aggregated traffic analytics.

If you attend one of our events, we will also maintain a record of this.

We also offer a service whereby individuals can post their resumes on our site.

We gather information about people who speak at our events for the purpose of promoting that event, and we may also hold data about people who write for our magazine or online publications.

If you make payments to AmCham China, we may also record information for tax purposes. However, we don’t hold specific payment information (such as credit card numbers) that you provide to the third-party payment vendors that we work with.

We may also collect information that is not directly associated with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose to the extent permissible under law.

**_How we use_** ** _this information_**

We use the information:

  * To verify the status of your membership
  * To provide you with membership privileges, including access to certain areas of the website
  * To promote you, your company, or an event or a publication that you are involved with
  * To contact you periodically with information about the chamber, events, newsletters, information, surveys, and third-party offers
  * For reporting purposes to government authorities or to meet relevant requirements under laws and regulations
  * For the benefit of auditors
  * To understand how our members use the chamber’s services
  * In our membership directory, both in print and online

**_Who We Share the Information With_**

In our Membership Directory, which we may sell or otherwise distribute to people outside the chamber, we acknowledge your membership of the chamber and provide general contact information for the company you work for.

We do share your information with third parties as described below:

  * As part of our Business Visa Service, we share with the US Embassy personal information that you provide us.
  * Third-party website developers have access to your information to help us analyze it and provide better services.
  * We may share your information with our service providers to the extent necessary, subject to confidentiality obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy.

When you provide your personal information on our website, you agree to our collection, use and provision of your information to third parties.

We **_don’t_** share personal information about you to third-party sites that help us conduct financial transactions. Nevertheless, you will likely provide them with sensitive information, and while we’ve done our best to ensure our partners’ systems are secure, we also can’t take responsibility for any unauthorized intrusions or system failures they suffer.

**_P_** ** _rotecting_** ** _Y_** ** _our_** ** _I_** ** _nformation_**

We take precautions to ensure your information is protected, but cannot guarantee that unauthorized intrusion or system failures won’t compromise the security of the data we hold. We use commercially reasonable efforts to cause our partners (including third party website developers) to protect your personal information in the event such information is collected or maintained by or shared with them.

We will notify you of any actual or potential leak, damage or loss of your personal information and take immediate remedial measures.

**_Our U_** ** _se of_** ** _C_** ** _ookies_**

When you visit our website, you agree to our use of cookies. A cookie is a small file created by the website on your computer that helps the site to identify your computer as a visitor. This might save you, for example, from having to log in every time you visit a new page or come back to the site later. We use only “first party” cookies, meaning that no third-party platforms will store or are able to request information from the cookies on your computer. 

**_How You Can M_** ** _odify or_** ** _D_** ** _elete_** ** _Your P_** ** _ersonal_** ** _I_** ** _nformation_** ** _or Preferences_**

At the bottom every email newsletter you receive from us, you can find an “unsubscribe” button that will remove you from the recipient list for that kind of email newsletter. You can also log in to the website to:

  * Change your personal information
  * Change email preferences

To remove your information from out databases, please contact [membership@amchamchina.com](mailto:membership@amchamchina.com), or call +86 (10) 8519 0800. You should understand that information we delete may still be held elsewhere in back-ups until those back-ups are updated.

**_When Our Privacy Policy Applies_**

Our Privacy Policy applies to all services offered by the chamber, but does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals.
